A Guide to the Episcopal Diocese of Southwestern Virginia 1905-1990
Digital Libraries and Archives, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- National Council--Field Department (219) 1934 (Box-folder 48-4)
- National Council--Department of Missions (221) 1934 (Box-folder 48-5)
- National Council--Department of Publicity (222) 1934 (Box-folder 48-6)
- National Council--Religious Education (223); National Council--Social Service (224) 1934 (Box-folder 48-7)
- : National Council--treasurer (226) 1934 (Box-folder 48-8)
- National Council--women's auxiliary (227) 1934 (Box-folder 48-9)
- News Notes (229); Notes (230) 1934 (Box-folder 48-10)
- Province of Washington--deaf mutes (235); Province of Washington--general (236) 1934 (Box-folder 48-11)
- Railways and Transportation (238) 1934 (Box-folder 48-12)
- Receipts (239) 1934 (Box-folder 48-13)
- St. Paul's School--Lawrenceville (240) 1934 (Box-folder 48-14)
- Southern Churchman (241); Southwestern Episcopalian (242) 1934 (Box-folder 48-15)
- Southwestern Episcopalian (242); Standing Committee (244) 1934 (Box-folder 48-16)
- Stuart Hall (245) 1934 (Box-folder 48-17)
- Stuart Hall (245) 1934 (Box-folder 48-18)
- Stuart Hall Fund Pledges (245A) 1934 (Box-folder 48-19)
- Summer Schools Sunday (246) 1934 (Box-folder 48-20)
- Theological Seminary (247) 1934 (Box-folder 48-21)
- Treasurer of the Diocese (248) 1934 (Box-folder 48-22)
- Trustees of the Diocese (249) 1934 (Box-folder 48-23)
- United Workers Thank You Offering (249A) 1934 (Box-folder 48-24)
- Vestries (250) 1934 (Box-folder 48-25)
- Virginia Episcopal School (251) 1934 (Box-folder 48-26)
- Visitations (253) 1934 (Box-folder 48-27)
- Women's Auxiliary (256) 1934 (Box-folder 48-28)
- Women's Auxiliary--outside of diocese (256A) 1934 (Box-folder 48-29)
- Women Workers (257) 1934 (Box-folder 48-30)
- Reverend H.H. Young (258) 1934 (Box-folder 48-31)
- Young People (259) 1934 (Box-folder 48-32)
- Diocesan Executive Board (308) 1934 (Box-folder 48-33)
- Box 49 1934-36
- Ellis Loan (317) 1934 (Box-folder 49-1)
- Letcher Gift--Richmond Securities (317) 1934 (Box-folder 49-2)
- Treasurer's Reports (317) 1934 (Box-folder 49-3)
- Woodson (317) 1934 (Box-folder 49-4)
- General Convention Matters (322) 1934 (Box-folder 49-5)
- Deaconess Blanche Adams 1934-35 (Box-folder 49-6)
- Reverend Charles O. Farrar 1934-35 (Box-folder 49-7)
- Lynchburg--St. Paul's (61) 1934-35 (Box-folder 49-8)
- Boys' Home--Covington (304) 1934-35 (Box-folder 49-9)
- Stuart Hall, Inc. (317) 1934-35 (Box-folder 49-10)
- Tompkins Loan (317) 1934-35 (Box-folder 49-11)
- Reverend William J. Gratton 1934-36 (Box-folder 49-12)
- Waring, John B.H. 1934-36 (Box-folder 49-13)
- President's Statements (303) 1934-36 (Box-folder 49-14)
- Wytheville Hotel Corporation (317) 1934-36 (Box-folder 49-15)
- Accountant's Report 1935 (Box-folder 49-16)
- Clergy 1935 (Box-folder 49-17)
- Council 1935 (Box-folder 49-18)
- Reverend Roderick H. Jackson 1935 (Box-folder 49-19)
- Ministries--inquiries for positions (A; M; P,) 1935 (Box-folder 49-20)
- Pension Fund (1935) 1935 (Box-folder 49-21)
- Scott, Thomas A. 1935 (Box-folder 49-22)
- St. John's Business Women's Chapter--minutes 1935 (Box-folder 49-23)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas' (2) 1935 (Box-folder 49-24)
- Altavista--St. Peter's (5) 1935 (Box-folder 49-25)
- Amherst--Ascension (1935: 6) 49-26 (Box-folder 49-26)
- Amherst--St. Paul's Mission (7) 1935 (Box-folder 49-27)
- Appalachia--Grace (8); Arrington--Trinity (9) 1935 (Box-folder 49-28)
- Bastian (9 1/2); Bedford--St. John's (10) 1935 (Box-folder 49-29)
- Bedford--St. Philip's (11); Big Island--St. Thomas' (12) 1935 (Box-folder 49-30)
- Big Stone Gap--Christ (13); Blacksburg--Christ (14) 1935 (Box-folder 49-31)
- Bluefield--St. Mary's (15) 1935 (Box-folder 49-32)
- Boonsboro--Trinity (16) 1935 (Box-folder 49-33)
- Bristol--Emmanuel (17) 1935 (Box-folder 49-34)
- Brookneal (18); Buchanan--Grace (19) 1935 (Box-folder 49-35)
- Buchanan--Trinity (20); Buena Vista--Christ (21) 1935 (Box-folder 49-36)
- Callaway--St. Peter's (22) 1935 (Box-folder 49-37)
- Christiansburg--St. Thomas (23); Clifford--St. Mary's (24) 1935 (Box-folder 49-38)
- Clifton Forge--St. Andrew's (25); Clintwood (26) 1935 (Box-folder 49-39)
- Covington--Emmanuel (27) 1935 (Box-folder 49-40)
- Dante--St. Mark's (29) 1935 (Box-folder 49-41)
- Drill--Mission (30); Eagle Rock--Emmanuel (31) 1935 (Box-folder 49-42)
- Endicott--St. John's (32) 1935 (Box-folder 49-43)
- Evington--Good Shepherd (33); Fincastle--St. Mark's (34) 1935 (Box-folder 49-44)
- Folly Mills--Good Shepherd (35); Forest--Ivy Chapel (36) 1935 (Box-folder 49-45)
- Glade Spring--Grace (38) 1935 (Box-folder 49-46)
- Glade Spring--Grace (38); Gladys--Christ (39) 1935 (Box-folder 49-47)
- Gladys--St. John's (39A) 1935 (Box-folder 49-48)
- Glasgow--St. John's (40) 1935 (Box-folder 49-49)
- Hot Springs--St. Luke's (41); Ivanhoe--St. Andrew's (42) 1935 (Box-folder 49-50)
- Lebanon--Mission (43); Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (44) 1935 (Box-folder 49-51)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (46); Lynchburg--Grace Memorial (47) 1935 (Box-folder 49-52)
- Lynchburg--St. John's (48); Lynchburg--St. Paul's (49) 1935 (Box-folder 49-53)
- Marion--Christ Church (51) 1935 (Box-folder 49-54)
- Martinsville--Christ (52) 1935 (Box-folder 49-55)
- Massies Mill--Grace (53); Montvale--St. Mark's (55) 1935 (Box-folder 49-56)
- Narrows--Our Savior (56); Nora--St. Stephen's (57) 1935 (Box-folder 49-57)
- Norton--All Saints (58); Norwood--Christ (59) 1935 (Box-folder 49-58)
- Pearisburg--Christ (60); Pedlar Mills--St. Luke's (61) 1935 (Box-folder 49-59)
- Pocahontas--Christ (62) 1935 (Box-folder 49-60)
- Pulaski--Christ (64) 1935 (Box-folder 49-61)
- Radford--Grace (65) 1935 (Box-folder 49-62)
- Richlands--Trinity (66) 1935 (Box-folder 49-63)
- Roanoke--Christ (67) 1935 (Box-folder 49-64)
- Roanoke--St. John's (68) 1935 (Box-folder 49-65)
- Roanoke--St. John's--history (68) 1935 (Box-folder 49-66)
- Box 50 1935
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (70) 1935 (Box-folder 50-1)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity (71) 1935 (Box-folder 50-2)
- St. Paul--Grace House-on-the-mountain (72) 1935 (Box-folder 50-3)
- Salem--St. Paul's (74); Saltville--St. Paul's (75) 1935 (Box-folder 50-4)
- Schuyler--Christ (76); Six Mile Bridge--Grace (77) 1935 (Box-folder 50-5)
- Splashdam--Mission (78); Staunton--Emmanuel (79) 1935 (Box-folder 50-6)
- Staunton--Trinity (80); Sweet Briar (81) 1935 (Box-folder 50-7)
- Tazewell--Stras Memorial (82); Verona--Emmanuel (83) 1935 (Box-folder 50-8)
- Waynesboro--St. John's (84) 1935 (Box-folder 50-9)
- Waynesboro--St. John's--history regarding Reverend Walter W. Clem (84) 1935 (Box-folder 50-10)
- Wytheville--St. John's (85) 1935 (Box-folder 50-11)
- E--general (91) 1935 (Box-folder 50-12)
- G--general (93); H--general (94) 1935 (Box-folder 50-13)
- K--general (97); L--general (98) 1935 (Box-folder 50-14)
- M--general (99) 1935 (Box-folder 50-15)
- N--general (100); O--general (101) 1935 (Box-folder 50-16)
- P-Q--general (102) 1935 (Box-folder 50-17)
- R--general (103); S--general (104) 1935 (Box-folder 50-18)
- T--general (105) 1935 (Box-folder 50-19)
- U-V--general (106) 1935 (Box-folder 50-20)
- #106 1935 (Box-folder 50-21)
- W--general (107); X-Y-Z--general (108) 1935 (Box-folder 50-22)
- Deaconess Adams (108A); American Church Building Fund Commission (109) 1935 (Box-folder 50-23)
- American Church Institute for Negroes (110); Auditor (113) 1935 (Box-folder 50-24)
- Automobiles (114); Berkeley, Edmund (114A) 1935 (Box-folder 50-25)
- Bishop's Discretionary Fund (117) 1935 (Box-folder 50-26)
- Blue Ridge Industrial School (118) 1935 (Box-folder 50-27)
- Boys' Home (119) 1935 (Box-folder 50-28)
- Burke, William Francis (119A); Chancellor of the Diocese (120) 1935 (Box-folder 50-29)
- Church Pension Fund (121) 1935 (Box-folder 50-30)
- Church School Lenten Offering (122) 1935 (Box-folder 50-31)
- Clergy Conference (124) 1935 (Box-folder 50-32)
- Clergy List (125); Coleman, Mrs. John F. (127A) 1935 (Box-folder 50-33)
- Communion Wine and Wafers (128); Consents (129) 1935 (Box-folder 50-34)
- Convocations (130); Council--church property (132) 1935 (Box-folder 50-35)
- Council--clerical support (133) 1935 (Box-folder 50-36)
- Council--constitution and canons (134) 1935 (Box-folder 50-37)
- Council--elections and credentials (136) 1935 (Box-folder 50-38)
- Council--general (138); Council--missionary night (142) 1935 (Box-folder 50-39)
- Council--program (145) 1935 (Box-folder 50-40)
- Council--reports (146) 1935 (Box-folder 50-41)
- Council--rural work (147); Council--secretary (148) 1935 (Box-folder 50-42)
- Daughters of the King (150); Depositions (151) 1935 (Box-folder 50-43)
- Diocesan Mission School (152) 1935 (Box-folder 50-44)
- Diocesan Office (153) 1935 (Box-folder 50-45)
- Educational Fund (155); Episcopal High School (156); Episcopal Residence (157) 1935 (Box-folder 50-46)
- Diocese of Virginia (154) 1935 (Box-folder 50-47)
- Examining Chaplains (159); Executive Board--Field Department (162) 1935 (Box-folder 50-48)
- Executive Board pledges (163); Executive Board--Department of Finance (164) 1935 (Box-folder 50-49)
- Executive Board--Department of Religious Education (166); Department of Social Service (167); Department of Publicity (165) 1935 (Box-folder 50-50)
- Executive Board--general (168); Executive Secretaries' Conference (169) 1935 (Box-folder 50-51)
- Ferrell, Edgar (170A); First National Exchange Bank (171) 1935 (Box-folder 50-52)
- Forward Movement (172) 1935 (Box-folder 50-53)
- Franklin County (172A); General Church Deficit (173); General Convention (174) 1935 (Box-folder 50-54)
- Box 51 1935
- General Convention--House of Bishops (175); General Convention--Presiding Bishop (176) 1935 (Box-folder 51-1)
- Girls Friendly (177); Good Friday Offering (178) 1935 (Box-folder 51-2)
- Historiographer (179); Industrial Work (179 1/2); Insurance (180) 1935 (Box-folder 51-3)
- Bishop Jett--personal (181) 1935 (Box-folder 51-4)
- Journal--Bishop's Address (182); Journal copy (183) 1935 (Box-folder 51-5)
- Journal--mailing list (184) 1935 (Box-folder 51-6)
- Journal--publisher (186) 1935 (Box-folder 51-7)
- Correspondence between Bishop Jett and Reverend Arthur E. Koch (186AA) 1935 (Box-folder 51-8)
- Lay Readers (188); Laymen's League (189) 1935 (Box-folder 51-9)
- Mr. T.G. Leek--Covington--Postulant (189A); Letcher, John D. (190) 1935 (Box-folder 51-10)
- Letters Dimissory (191); Lewis, Thomas D., Jr. (191A) 1935 (Box-folder 51-11)
- Library (192); Little, Haskin (192A) 1935 (Box-folder 51-12)
- A.G. Lively, Jr. (192B) 1935 (Box-folder 51-13)
- Living Church (193); Living Church Annual (193A) 1935 (Box-folder 51-14)
- Mimeograph and Circular Letters (196); Meyers, Edward DeLos (197A) 1935 (Box-folder 51-15)
- National Council--Department of Domestic Missions (198) 1935 (Box-folder 51-16)
- National Council--Department of Foreign Missions (199); National Council--Department of Christian Social Service (200) 1935 (Box-folder 51-17)
- National Council--Field Department (201) 1935 (Box-folder 51-18)
- National Council--Department of Publicity (203); National Council--Department of Religious Education (204) 1935 (Box-folder 51-19)
- National Council--Department of Religous Education (204) 1935 (Box-folder 51-20)
- National Council--President (205) 1935 (Box-folder 51-21)
- Baptisms (205A) 1935 (Box-folder 51-22)
- National Council--Treasurer (206) 1935 (Box-folder 51-23)
- National Council--Women's Auxiliary (207) 1935 (Box-folder 51-24)
- News Notes (208); Notes--bank (209) 1935 (Box-folder 51-25)
- Ordinations (209 1/2); Pastoral Letters (209 3/4) 1935 (Box-folder 51-26)
- Prayer Book (210A) 1935 (Box-folder 51-27)
- Province of Washington--deaf mutes (211) 1935 (Box-folder 51-28)
- Province of Washington--general (212) 1935 (Box-folder 51-29)
- Province of Washington--synod (213) 1935 (Box-folder 51-30)
- Railways and Transportation (214) 1935 (Box-folder 51-31)
- Inquiries for Ministry Positions (B; C; D G; H, 215) 1935 (Box-folder 51-32)
- Receipts (215) 1935 (Box-folder 51-33)
- Wilfred E. Roach--Martinsville, Virginia (215A) 1935 (Box-folder 51-34)
- St. Paul's School--Lawrenceville (216) 1935 (Box-folder 51-35)
- Southern Churchman (218) 1935 (Box-folder 51-36)
- Southwestern Episcopalian (219) 1935 (Box-folder 51-37)
- Southwestern Episcopalian (219A) 1935 (Box-folder 51-38)
- Standing Committee (221) 1935 (Box-folder 51-39)
- Stuart Hall (222) 1935 (Box-folder 51-40)
- Stuart Hall (Folder 1 of 2, 222) 1935 (Box-folder 51-41)
- Stuart Hall (Folder 2 of 2, 222) 1935 (Box-folder 51-42)
- Stuart Hall--statistical figures (222A) 1935 (Box-folder 51-43)
- Summer Schools--sundry (223): Terry, Miss Lucinda (223A) 1935 (Box-folder 51-44)
- Theological Seminary (224) 1935 (Box-folder 51-45)
- Treasurer of the Diocese (225) 1935 (Box-folder 51-46)
- Trustees of the Diocese (226) 1935 (Box-folder 51-47)
- United Thank Offerings--workers (227) 1935 (Box-folder 51-48)
- Vestries (228) 1935 (Box-folder 51-49)
- Virginia Episcopal School (229) 1935 (Box-folder 51-50)
- Visitations (230) 1935 (Box-folder 51-51)
- Mrs. Schuyler Vokmar (230 1/2); The Witness (231) 1935 (Box-folder 51-52)
- Women's Auxiliary--diocesan (235) 1935 (Box-folder 51-53)
- Box 52 1935-37
- Women's Auxiliary--outside of diocese (233) 1935 (Box-folder 52-1)
- Women Workers--general (234) 1935 (Box-folder 52-2)
- Young People (235) 1935 (Box-folder 52-3)
- Young People's Conference--Virginia Episcopal School--Lynchburg--June 10-13 (236) 1935 (Box-folder 52-4)
- Diocesan Executive Board (308) 1935 (Box-folder 52-5)
- Lambert's Point Tow Boat (317) 1935 (Box-folder 52-6)
- Letcher Gift--Richmond Securities (317) 1935 (Box-folder 52-7)
- Treasurer--general correspondence (317) 1935 (Box-folder 52-8)
- Treasurer's Reports (317) 1935 (Box-folder 52-9)
- Clergy--Reverend W. Francis Allison 1935-36 (Box-folder 52-10)
- Reverend Victor E. Holly 1935-36 (Box-folder 52-11)
- Appeals (11) 1935-36 (Box-folder 52-12)
- T--general (105) 1935-36 (Box-folder 52-13)
- Auditor (113) 1935-36 (Box-folder 52-14)
- National Council--Women's Auxiliary (207) 1935-36 (Box-folder 52-15)
- Southwestern Episcopalian (219) 1935-36 (Box-folder 52-16)
- Stuart Hall (222) 1935-36 (Box-folder 52-17)
- Episcopal Residence Committee (315) 1935-36 (Box-folder 52-18)
- Reverend Ernest A. Harding 1935-37 (Box-folder 52-19)
- Hutton, Reverend S. Janney 1935-37 (Box-folder 52-20)
- Guerry, Reverend Edward B. (126) 1935-37 (Box-folder 52-21)
- Burgoon, Reverend Charles P. 1936 (Box-folder 52-22)
- Council 1936 (Box-folder 52-23)
- Council--May 19-20 1936 (Box-folder 52-24)
- Ministries--inquiries for positions (B; N; P) 1936 (Box-folder 52-25)
- Pension Fund 1936 (Box-folder 52-26)
- St. John's Business Women's Chapter--minutes 1936 (Box-folder 52-27)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas (2); Altavista--St. Peter's (5) 1936 (Box-folder 52-28)
- Amherst--Ascension (6); Amherst--St. Paul's (Bear Mountain, 7) 1936 (Box-folder 52-29)
- Appalachia--Grace (8); Arrington--Trinity (9); Bedford--St. John's (10) 1936 (Box-folder 52-30)
- Bedford--St. Philip's (11); Big Island--St. Thomas (12); Big Stone Gap--Christ (13) 1936 (Box-folder 52-31)
- Bluefield--St. Mary's (15); Blacksburg--Christ (14) 1936 (Box-folder 52-32)
- Boonesboro--Trinity (16); Bristol--Emmanuel (17) 1936 (Box-folder 52-33)
- Brookneal (18); Buchanan--Grace (19); Buchanan--Trinity (20) 1936 (Box-folder 52-34)
- Buena Vista--Christ (21); Callaway--St. Peter's (22) 1936 (Box-folder 52-35)
- Christiansburg--St. Thomas (23); Clifford--St. Mark's (24); Clifton Forge (25) 1936 (Box-folder 52-36)
- Clintwood (26); Covington--Emmanuel (27) 1936 (Box-folder 52-37)
- Dante--St. Mark's (29) 1936 (Box-folder 52-38)
- Eagle Rock--Emmanuel (31); Endicott--St. John's (32) 1936 (Box-folder 52-39)
- Evington--Good Shepherd (33); Fincastle--St. Mark's (34); Folly Mills--Good Shepherd (35) 1939 (Box-folder 52-40)
- Forest--Ivy Chapel (36); Glade Spring--Grace (38); Gladys--Christ (39) 1936 (Box-folder 52-41)
- Glasgow--St. John's (40); Hot Springs--St. Luke's (41) 1936 (Box-folder 52-42)
- Ivanhoe--St. Andrew's (42); Lebanon Mission (43); Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (44) 1936 (Box-folder 52-43)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (46); Lynchburg--Grace Memorial (47); Lynchburg--St. John's (48) 1936 (Box-folder 52-44)
- Lynchburg--St. Paul's (49); Madison Heights--Emmanuel (50) 1936 (Box-folder 52-45)
- Box 53 1936
- Marion--Christ (51) 1936 (Box-folder 53-1)
- Martinsville--Christ (52); Massies Mill--Grace (53); Montvale--St. Mark's (55) 1936 (Box-folder 53-2)
- Nora--St. Stephen's (51); Norton--All Saints (58); Norwood--Christ (59) 1936 (Box-folder 53-3)
- Pearisburg--Christ (60); Pedlar Mills--St. Luke's (61); Pocahontas--Christ (62) 1936 (Box-folder 53-4)
- Pulaski--Christ (64) 1936 (Box-folder 53-5)
- Radford--Grace (65); Richland--Trinity (66); Roanoke--Christ (67) 1936 (Box-folder 53-6)
- Roanoke--St. John's (68) 1936 (Box-folder 53-7)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (70) 1936 (Box-folder 53-8)
- St. Paul--Grace House (72) 1936 (Box-folder 53-9)
- Salem--Mt. Gerizim (73) 1936 (Box-folder 53-10)
- Salem--St. Paul's (74) 1936 (Box-folder 53-11)
- Saltville--St. Paul's (75) 1936 (Box-folder 53-12)
- Schuyler--Christ (76) 1936 (Box-folder 53-13)
- Six Mile Bridge--Grace (77) 1936 (Box-folder 53-14)
- Splashdam--Mission (78) 1936 (Box-folder 53-15)
- Staunton--Emmanuel (79) 1936 (Box-folder 53-16)
- Staunton--Trinity (80) 1936 (Box-folder 53-17)
- Tazewell--Stras Memorial (82) 1936 (Box-folder 53-18)
- Verona--Emmanuel (83) 1936 (Box-folder 53-19)
- Waynesboro--St. John's (84) 1936 (Box-folder 53-20)
- Wytheville--St. John's (85) 1936 (Box-folder 53-21)
- Yards--Mission (86) 1936 (Box-folder 53-22)
- A--general (87) 1936 (Box-folder 53-23)
- B--general (88) 1936 (Box-folder 53-24)
- C--general (89) 1936 (Box-folder 53-25)
- D--general (90) 1936 (Box-folder 53-26)
- F--general (92) 1936 (Box-folder 53-27)
- G--general (93) 1936 (Box-folder 53-28)
- H--general (94) 1936 (Box-folder 53-29)
- I--general (95) 1936 (Box-folder 53-30)
- J--general (96) 1936 (Box-folder 53-31)
- K--general (97) 1936 (Box-folder 53-32)
- L--general (98) 1936 (Box-folder 53-33)
- M--general (99) 1936 (Box-folder 53-34)
- N--general (100) 1936 (Box-folder 53-35)
- P-Q--general (102) 1936 (Box-folder 53-36)
- R--general (103) 1936 (Box-folder 53-37)
- S--general (104) 1936 (Box-folder 53-38)
- U-V--general (106) 1936 (Box-folder 53-39)
- W--general (107) 1936 (Box-folder 53-40)
- X-Y-Z--general (108) 1936 (Box-folder 53-41)
- American Church Building Fund (109) 1936 (Box-folder 53-42)
- American Church Institute for Negroes (110) 1936 (Box-folder 53-43)
- Automobiles (114) 1936 (Box-folder 53-44)
- Berkeley, Edmund (114A) 1936 (Box-folder 53-45)
- Birthday Thank Offering (116) 1936 (Box-folder 53-46)
- Bishop's Discretionary Fund (117) 1936 (Box-folder 53-47)
- Blue Ridge Industrial School (118) 1936 (Box-folder 53-48)
- Boys' Home (119) 1936 (Box-folder 53-49)
- Church Pension Fund (121) 1936 (Box-folder 53-50)
- Clergy Conference (124) 1936 (Box-folder 53-51)
- Consents (129) 1936 (Box-folder 53-52)
- Box 54 1936
- Convocations (130) 1936 (Box-folder 54-1)
- Council--clerical support (133) 1936 (Box-folder 54-2)
- Council--elections and credentials (136) 1936 (Box-folder 54-3)
- Council--general (138) 1936 (Box-folder 54-4)
- Council--hospitality (139) 1936 (Box-folder 54-5)
- Council--minutes (141) 1936 (Box-folder 54-6)
- Council--Missionary Night (142) 1936 (Box-folder 54-7)
- Council--New Parishes and Missions (143); Council--parochial reports (144) 1936 (Box-folder 54-8)
- Council--program (145) 1936 (Box-folder 54-9)
- Council--reports (146) 1936 (Box-folder 54-10)
- Council--rural work (147) 1936 (Box-folder 54-11)
- Council--secretary (148) 1936 (Box-folder 54-12)
- Council--commission on the support and finances of the diocese (148A) 1936 (Box-folder 54-13)
- Daughters of the King (150); Depositions (151) 1936 (Box-folder 54-14)
- Diocesan Office (153) 1936 (Box-folder 54-15)
- Diocesan Records (154) 1936 (Box-folder 54-16)
- Educational Fund (155) 1936 (Box-folder 54-17)
- Episcopal High School (156) 1936 (Box-folder 54-18)
- Examining Chaplains (159) 1936 (Box-folder 54-19)
- Executive Board--secretary's attention (161) 1936 (Box-folder 54-20)
- Executive Board--Field Department (162) 1936 (Box-folder 54-21)
- Field Department--pledges (163) 1936 (Box-folder 54-22)
- Executive Board--Department of Finance (164) 1936 (Box-folder 54-23)
- Executive Board--Department of Publicity (165) 1936 (Box-folder 54-24)
- Executive Board--Department of Religious Education (166) 1936 (Box-folder 54-25)
- Executive Board--Department of Social Service (167) 1936 (Box-folder 54-26)
- Executive Board--general (168) 1936 (Box-folder 54-27)
- Federal Council of Churches (170) 1936 (Box-folder 54-28)
- Edgar Ferrell (170A) 1936 (Box-folder 54-29)
- First National Exchange Bank (171) 1936 (Box-folder 54-30)
- Forward Movement (172) 1936 (Box-folder 54-31)
- General Church Deficit (173) 1936 (Box-folder 54-32)
- General Convention (174) 1936 (Box-folder 54-33)
- General Convention--House of Bishops (175) 1936 (Box-folder 54-34)
- General Convention--Presiding Bishop (176); Good Friday Offering (178) 1936 (Box-folder 54-35)
- Industrial Work (179 1/2) 1936 (Box-folder 54-36)
- Insurance (180) 1936 (Box-folder 54-37)
- Bishop Jett--personal (181) 1936 (Box-folder 54-38)
- Journal--copy (183); Journal--mailing list (184) 1936 (Box-folder 54-39)
- Journal--publisher (186) 1936 (Box-folder 54-40)
- Correspondence Between Bishop Jett and Reverend Arthur E. Koch (186AA) 1936 (Box-folder 54-41)
- Laymen's League (189); Letcher, Colonel John D. (190) 1936 (Box-folder 54-42)
- Letters Dimissory (191); Lewis, Thomas D., Jr.--admitted postulant March 17, 1934 (191A) 1936 (Box-folder 54-43)
- Library (192) 1936 (Box-folder 54-44)
- Little, Haskin (192A) 1936 (Box-folder 54-45)
- Lively, A.G., Jr. (192B); Living Church (193) 1936 (Box-folder 54-46)
- Living Church Annual (194); MacClintock, Ronald--postulant (194A) 1936 (Box-folder 54-47)
- Motion Pictures (197) 1936 (Box-folder 54-48)
- Box 55 1936-54
- De Los Myers, Dr. Edward (197A) 1936 (Box-folder 55-1)
- National Council--Department of Domestic Missions (198) 1936 (Box-folder 55-2)
- National Council--Department of Foreign Missions (199); National Council--Department of Church Social Service (200) 1936 (Box-folder 55-3)
- National Council--Field Department (201) 1936 (Box-folder 55-4)
- National Council--Department of Publicity (203) 1936 (Box-folder 55-5)
- National Council--President (205) 1936 (Box-folder 55-6)
- National Council--Treasurer (206) 1936 (Box-folder 55-7)
- News Notes (208) 1936 (Box-folder 55-8)
- Pastoral Letters (209 3/4) 1936 (Box-folder 55-9)
- Postulants (210) 1936 (Box-folder 55-10)
- Province of Washington--deaf mutes (211) 1936 (Box-folder 55-11)
- Synod (213) 1936 (Box-folder 55-12)
- Railways and Transportation (214) 1936 (Box-folder 55-13)
- Receipts (215) 1936 (Box-folder 55-14)
- Roach, Wilfred E. (215A) 1936 (Box-folder 55-15)
- St. Paul's School--Lawrenceville (216) 1936 (Box-folder 55-16)
- Southern Churchman (218) 1936 (Box-folder 55-17)
- Southwestern Episcopalian--accounts (219A) 1936 (Box-folder 55-18)
- Standing Committee (221) 1936 (Box-folder 55-19)
- Stuart Hall, Inc. (222) 1936 (Box-folder 55-20)
- Summer Schools and Conferences (223) 1936 (Box-folder 55-21)
- Theological Seminary (224) 1936 (Box-folder 55-22)
- The Torok Case (224A) 1936 (Box-folder 55-23)
- Treasurer of the Diocese (225) 1936 (Box-folder 55-24)
- Trustees of the Diocese (226) 1936 (Box-folder 55-25)
- United Thank Offering--general (227) 1936 (Box-folder 55-26)
- Vestries (228) 1936 (Box-folder 55-27)
- Virginia Episcopal School (229) 1936 (Box-folder 55-28)
- Visitations (230) 1936 (Box-folder 55-29)
- Volkmar, Mrs. Schuyler (230A) 1936 (Box-folder 55-30)
- The Witness (231) 1936 (Box-folder 55-31)